With this, both the Summer and Autumn Dream Tickets...
all Dream Tickets are in my possession.
I won't let you get away with this!
We're gonna catch you and take our coords back!
Those commoners are not fit to wear them.
And they are vital to the exchange.
But should I say as such yet?
The smiles will surely vanish from their faces this time.
Happy Halloween!
Open that hidden door
himitsu no tobira wo akeyou
There's no need to be shy – within lies the wonderland of your dreams
hazukashigaranaide soko wa suteki na wandaarando
I wanna bring about a world all of my own
dare mo ga mita koto nai you na
Like nothing you've ever seen
watashi dake no sekai meikingu shiyou
Go on and bring all your friends
tomodachi mitsukete sasottara
This passport connects all lands and crosses all borders
sore wa unmei no suteeji he
It leads you to your destined stage
tsunagaru (tsuzuku) saikou no pasupooto
Let's go!
let's go
Dreams are made to come true, so seize that chance
yume wa kanaeru mono chansu ni tsunageyou
You can be the idol you've always dreamed of being
akogareteiru aidoru mezashite
We can all bring about a miracle together
minna de issho ni kiseki okosou yo
That shining, radiant
kirakira kagayakidasu
PriPara Fantasy
PriParis fantajii
Have a Good Fright
And a Happy Halloween!
Happy Halloween!
We have some special coords for this All Hallows' Eve!
SoLaMi SMILE's members features all sorts of Halloween elements.
Monster Bat Coord!
And Dressing Pafé is spruced up in luxurious fluffy fake fur!
Monster Ghost Coord!
You look wonderful!
It's time for the once-in-a-year Halloween event!
Let's have a blast!
Yay...
Um...
I know we're bummed out that Phantom Thief Genius stole our coords,
but we'll get them back. Meganii promised, remember?
Besides, if we're sad, then that means the phantom gets what he wants.
Yeah, he'd be happier than anyone!
I don't like that.
It feels like we're just doing what he wants.
That sucks!
Yeah!
All right!
Let's have a blast!
Yep!
You said it, Laala-pri!
Happy Halloween!
Go!
Uh, so...
Yes, it seems dressing up as Phantom Thief Genius
is really in vogue this Halloween.
Dressing up as him?
Even though he's a stinking thief?
There are those who hate him...
and those who find him charming, as well!
The heart wants what it wants.
Meganee.
What are those coords?
This way, baby!
Ah.
Those unique coords are another big trend
from this year: local mascot dresses!
Local mascot dresses?
I like it!
They take inspiration from specialty goods Japan over!
Looking good!
Amazing! Simply ravishing!
They're really one of a kind!
Very nice!
They're gorgeous! I want to wear one too!
Give us a smile!
There are so many concepts here!
Look this way!
So many homegrown specialties!
And a jump!
Now jump for me!
Show me that smile!
Mm, gorgeous!
You all look frightfully wonderful tonight.
The costume contest will begin shortly!
Happy Halloween!
Presiding over the contest will be these and the other mascots judges!
FRIGHTS!!
The person who gathers the most frights wins!
The winner will be bestowed a splendid crown and the title of "Miss Halloween"!
Don your most wonderful costume...
Make my and the judges hearts...
tremble.
Make them... tremble.
Make them tremble!
"Miss Halloween"...
All fright, that's super duper cool!
This sounds fun!
It's Laala!
Long time no spook, Laala!
I feel like someone just said my name...
It could have been a ghost...
Hey, come on, Mirei!
I had a fearing I'd see you here!
Help! It's a lantern monster!
I'm so happy you remember me!
Hi there, old friends and new friends.
I'm Rantern! Pleased to scare you!
Pleased to scare you...
But you're really a ghost, right, Rantern?
What's got your pri-tches in a knot?
Take a closer look-pri.
She's got legs and everything-pri.
Mirei's fright! I'm a human!
A human...
You're jumping at shadows!
Jumping at shadows
You're predispositioned to expect something scary, so any stimulus provokes fright.
Capisce...
Deruderubii...
Deruderubii!
FRIGHTS
Shirai Nanami
Takahashi Toriko
Mika Inoue
Kurosu Aroma
Well! Aroma has leapt into the top spot!
Kuma!
What... convincing acting-usa.
Hm?
I thought you and Mikan both hated snakes, though?
Perhaps, but an imitation serpent is all the more adorable!
Volume 1031, chapter 66 of the prophetic grimoire Aroma:
take the form of the wicked and
become the harvest festival queen!
It means Aroma's gonna be Miss Halloween!
How nice...
That reminds me; Ran, you loved horror so much...
that you went to train at its home, Horriwood, right?
Oh, fright...
What? You've been to the one and only Horriwood which I, too, yearned for?
Horriwood, crucible of all things horror, where kindred spirits gather! How I've longed to go!
Wow!
F–Fright...
How suspicious.
Who is?
Have you truly been admitted to Horriwood?
I have my doubts.
You're not the least bit frightening!
I have to say, Rantern's a lot more...
She's really cute!
No!
They're all getting scared away by my cuteness...
And thus I can declare:
You're far from terrifying! Your paltry
fearsomeness is far outclassed by this!
How perfectly peculiar!
What on earth is that bizarre creature?
It's Neko before she puts on her makeup!
Scary!
Will you stop kitten around?
FRIGHTS
Matsubara Teiko
Kurosu Aroma
Shirai Nanami
Takahashi Toriko
Matsubara Teiko
Kurosu Aroma
Shirai Nanami
Tochiotome Love
Hm? Hey, where'd Ran go?
I think she was so shocked she ran off.
What?
Rantern!
What's wrong?
Everyone's costumes are too amazing...
That's not true, Rantern!
But I ended up dropping out of Horriwood!
What?
But why?
Every time I tried to do horror makeup, it turns out cute...
I tried going to Horriwood to learn how to do it properly, but it just turned out worse!
Rantern...
Like...
My rokurokubi's necks wound up in bow knots...
My Yuki-onna winds up commenting on how warm it is...
It's not cold at all.
Even when I dressed up as the classic villain from the 13th-generation Chainsaw Brothers,
I brandished a towel instead of a chainsaw!
I'm pri amazed you can even get it that wrong...
That's why I dropped out of Horriwood.
I become the bottom rank...
So you went to study horror,
but you developed your skills in cute makeup instead-pri.
I'd be pretty upset...
I know!
My mum says in times like this, you just need to believe in yourself.
If you can only make yourself look cute,
we'll help you with some scary makeup!
Really?
Could you? Would you?
I fear-y, fear-y wanna be Miss Halloween!
Let's all pitch in!
Pri!
Yes!
Oh no! Oh no!
He's coming!
Ooh! I'm coming to suck your blood!
Oh no!
I'm on my last legs. I can't run anymore-chanko!
He's going to plunge his fangs into my sweet, maidenly neck!
Chanko.
Chanko?
The nape of your neck...
should only be given to the one you love most.
Meganii...
You don't have to hold back, you know-chanko.
Glasses flash!
So bright!
He's running away-chanko!
I'm still in a Dalí-mma over my Halloween costume!
As an art teacher, I must produce a costume that brings wonder and inspiration-Da Vinci!
My mind's a blank canvas...
Sir Ham, you've solved the Da Vinci code-Da Vinci!
Thank-ubrick!
I'm decided and I'm ready to throw down Rodin!
Devi!
Meet my gaze and be turned to stone!
Stop-tori! I don't want to be stone!
Make sure you vote for Aroma plenty!
Okay-tori!
Please don't freeze my supple skin-tori!
FRIGHTS
Fifteen minutes remain until the costume contest ends!
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
Matsubara Teiko
Shirai Nanami
Aroma, in her arresting Medusa costume,
has attained 58,114 frights!
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
Matsubara Teiko
Shirai Nanami
Kurosu Aroma
Her lead is unchallenged!
S–Snake!
Aroma.
I thought you liked snakes?
We can't handle the real thing!
But I went to all the trouble...
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
Matsubara Teiko
Shirai Nanami
Oh my! Fuwari, brandishing a real snake, has leapt into first place!
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
Matsubara Teiko
Midorikaze Fuwari
I guess you can't beat the horror of nature.
Fuwari's just got first place.
We can't lose to her, Ran!
It's complete!
It's Red Flash makeup!
That's you from the pri-vious year.
No, that's not it.
This time is the 20-year aged Kishu red plum.
See how it's a deeper colour and has lovely puckered skin?
Are you scared? I'm all sour and salty!
Yep, she's sure cute-kuma!
Next up is my shot-pri!
To beat a snake,
we need its arch enemy-pri!
Fright, now I'm a mongoose!
She's really cute-usa!
Curses!
True, it's the natural foe of the pit viper,
but this costume has only multi-pri-ed her cuteness!
You'd better dish up something pri spine-chilling!
Spine-chilling?
A ghost-pri.
Capisce!
All done!
So cute!
She's like a teru teru bozu charm-nekon.
Her face looks so friendly!
When you said "ghost", this was all I could think of.
I'm sorry, Ran.
I couldn't do it right after all...
It's fine!
You all did your best to help me.
I can't help what I look like, fright?
She's so cute!
All right, we're done!
Sizzling okonomiyaki!
Sizzle, sizzle!
Si... zzle...
How perfectly peculiar...
What on earth are we wearing?
Monja outfits, of course.
We'll take the Miss Halloween crown and advertise our store at the same time.
That's scamming two ostriches at once!
What? It's "two birds with one stone"!
Dun-dun-Rodin!
Da Vin...
Da Vi–
... nci.
That statue's moving!
What in blazes?
Get away from it!
What's going on?
I'm coming too!
Dun-dun-Rodin!
Don't try and supp-Renaissance your surprise!
You'll remem-brandt this forever:
it's Ajimi The Thinker.
Wha? This statue is Ajimi?
Rodin's "Thinker"-pri?
A walking statue...
a sculpture standing before me makes my heart tremble-nekon!
Now this is living art-kuma!
Spam those frights-usa!
FRIGHTS
Midorikaze Fuwari
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
Matsubara Teiko
Midorikaze Fuwari
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
Kiki Ajimi
What a turnaround!
Midorikaze Fuwari
Kurosu Aroma
Tochiotome Love
With only five minutes remaining,
Ajimi has surpassed Fuwari and leapt into first place!
Kiki Ajimi
I did it-Picasa-Da Vinci!
I'm Cézanne the title of Miss Halloween!
Curses, again and again...
You shall be free of curses!
Aroma's saying she's kind of mad!
Fright...
These watery depths...
were really awful!
The costume event has now concluded!
PriPara
COSTUME CONTEST
HAPPY HALLOWEEN
Ran
And so,
Ran has become Miss Halloween!
Congratulations, Ran!
Congratulations, Ran-pri!
Thank you scary much!
Thanks to all of you, I was able to become Miss Halloween! All fright!
I want to thank you all! For this performance,
will you let me do your makeup and styling?
Capisce!
I'm sure your makeup sense will pri-pel us to greater heights of cuteness!
Scan the appropriate number of MyTickets for your coord.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Starting the Coord Change.
To celebrate the winner of the costume contest, Ran,
today we have a special Number One Coord!
Idol Grand Prix Number One Coord!
With the brilliant neon sewn into the dress,
you'll shine bright as the glittering stage!
Idol Grand Prix Number One Honey Coord!
Pri!
The "Number One" logo has been designed...
with a lovely big ribbon and a heart-shaped crest!
Idol Grand Prix Number One Honey Coord!
Pretty!
pretty
Paradise!
paradise
Ran's makeup is perfect for getting everyone fired up!
Yes!
yes
We can make dreams!
we can make dream
I've been yearning for this excitement
matteta konna tokimeki
Where's the fun in being alone? Come over here
hitorikiri ja mottainai kocchi ni kite
And sing!
utaou
We can bring forth a miracle when we're together
issho ni kanaeru kiseki
This miracle
kiseki
Send our wishes to the sky
todokasetai sora made
Freely – merrily – jump!
soukai zenkai jump
No matter where it seems you're going
donna jibun ni natte mitai darou
Or who you'll become
dare datte
We can all sketch our own futures
ashita wo sukecchi shichau kara
Don't you want to see that shining tomorrow?
kirakira kagayaite mitakunai
We all have a ticket in our hearts
haato ni chiketto wa motta yo
Yes, we do
sou motta yo
Let's take the next step
tsugi no suteppu yume no suteeji
To the stage of our dreams
tobidasou
Our hearts shine prismatic
kokoro wa purizumu mitai da ne
Yes, they are
sou da de
Our melodies dyed iridescent
omoi no merodii kasanatta iro
Making drama, switch on!
An infinite rainbow
reinbou
We can become anything
nan ni datte nareru yo
Because we all believe
minna ga shinjiteru kara
Welcome
to our
Halloween night!
Yes!
yes
There we go!
Trick or Treat! Halloween Party!
Cyalume Change!
Let's always keep smiling
itsudemo egao de aou yo
No matter who we become
donna jibun mo
No matter what dream
donna mirai mo
We're free to choose
eranjaou
Our hearts are the tickets we need
haato ga chiketto ni natta yo
They came true
kanatta yo
We're burning to take the next step
tsugi no suteppu yume no suteeji
To the stage of our dreams
hashaijae
It suffuses our prismatic hearts
kokoro no purizumu wo tooshite
Just take a peek
nozoite
I'm sure the future in store is a marvellous paradise
mieta mirai wa kitto suteki na paradaisu
And it's open for everyone
minna datte nareru yo
So come over here
kocchi e kite
We're waiting for you
mattetanda yo
Come over so we can play
hayaku issho ni asobou
Yes!
yes
We can make dreams!
we can make dream
That was great!
What an amazing performance!
Thanks!
Miss Ran!
There you are!
I'm glad I caught you.
Fright?
Someone from Proadway who saw that performance...
wanted to invite you to join them as a makeup artist!
What?
You mean the Proadway? From New Yorp?
That's amazing!
Congratulations! What a fantastic opportunity!
I can't believe it! Getting to work on the stage...
It's a giant creep forward!
Isn't that great? Way to go-pri!
Let's all snap PriTickets to celebrateko!
All right!
One, two and...
Here!
Woo-hoo!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Ran!
Let's go and get something to eat-pri!
I'm so happy it feels like I'm floating!
Ran just...
Disa-pri-eared!
She–
She was a...
She was a ghost after all!
Owie-owie-owie...
Wait up, you guys...
I'm fright here!
Wait, no!
Leave some prankfurters for me!
You will, fright?
minna de warattara
kitto niji ga kakaru yo
When we all smile together, I'm sure a rainbow will connect us
doremifa sora ni rainbow melody♪
tsukuro! saikou no stage♪
Sing do-re-mi above the clouds and make a rainbow melody
te wo tsunaide kureta kara ne + issho ni ite kureta kara ne
It's because you took my hand, and it's because you're here for me
dakara dekitanda yo = mirakuru na dorama ga! (Yeah!)
That we were able to make this marvellous drama (Yeah!)
nachuraru ni hibiki aeru
egaichaeba kasanarunda ne
Our voices in unison – take a brush and the strokes blend naturally
sore wa kiseki mitai na harmony
Our beautiful harmony is miraculous
PriParis! utattara minna tomodachi da yo ne
PriPara! Let our voices free, and we'll all be friends
suteki na sumairu no anata wo mattetanda yo!
I've waited to see your brilliant smile!
hora mite! utattara melody, niji ni naru kara
Now try it: our melody becomes a rainbow
watashitachi no sora wo kazatte suteeji ni shiyou
Adorning our own sky; now, come on and sing
kokoro kirakira, rainbow melody♪
yume wa kanau yo!
The rainbow melody shining in our hearts makes our dreams come true
Next Episode
I'm making a PriPara Police team-Da Vinci!
Capisce!
Make it through your training and catch the Phantom Thief Genius-Da Vinci!
Oh no! He caught us instead!
Perilous PriPara Police
Holler at the Forefront
Next time, Perilous PriPara Police, Holler at the Forefront.